panzoid.com 2017-03-23

# Privacy Policy - Panzoid

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form, or use one of our online tools. 

When registering on our site or sending feedback, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

When using our online tools, occasionally data may be sent to Panzoid about your usage experience. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

Information sent about the use of our tools is solely for the purposes of improving your experience and will never be used to identify you. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Panzoid.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.panzoid.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on panzoid.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Panzoid.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Panzoid.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the forums and going to the 'My Profile' page. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at panzoid.com/terms

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 7/10/2014
